# **Stan Kazovsky**

Derby, Derbyshire

• Phone: 07852988281

• Email: stan.kazovsky@yahoo.com

• Portfolio: ciridae.co.uk/github

• Certification: shorturl.at/GLOS9

#### **ABOUT ME**

Enthusiastic Junior Software Developer, eager to contribute to the team success through hard work, attention to detail and excellent organizational skills. Clear understanding of HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Python (including Flask and Django). Trained in coding by Code Institute and CodeCademy. Motivated to learn, grow and excel in providing software to every industry.

### **WORK HISTORY**

## Junior Python Developer Al Global Media, Burton-on-Trent

August 2021 to Present

- Web scraping
- Analyzing business needs of clients and assisting in determining what resources and strategies to employ
- Collaborating closely with upper management to drive strategy through development and implementation of new processes

## Junior Software Developer

## Ciridae LTD, Derby

October 2020 to August 2021

- Liaised with clients politely and professionally to maintain excellent working relationships
- Full stack developer
- · Wrote clean, clear and well-tested code

## Volunteer Software Developer

#### **Fight Pandemics**

August 2020 to October 2020

- Fight Pandemics is a platform, where over 1000 volunteers created an environment, that allows communities to respond effectively to crises
- Front-end developer
- English to Polish translator

### Logistics Operative

## Gardner Aerospace, Derby

March 2019 to August 2020

- Delivered company products with great care and professional manners
- Planned, scheduled and delegated daily work
- Organised work to meet demanding production goals

#### **HGV** Driver

## Various companies

July 2017 to March 2019

## **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

College diploma

**Code Institute (Learning People)** - Online college December 2020

Second Class Honours Diploma in Software Development

#### **GED**

**John Paul 2nd College** - Zdunska Wola, Poland May 2010

A-levels in History, Math, Chemistry, Geography, Polish and English

## **HOBBIES**

I love reading, my favourite writers are Tolkien, Pratchett, Sanderson and Rothfuss, but I also like Gaarder, Sapkowski and other non-English writers. I practice ballroom dance and Aikido. My favourite holiday activity is mountain hiking.

## **LANGUAGES**

- Polish native
- English Master or Proficient
- Spanish Upper Intermediate
- · Russian Intermediate

### **SKILLS & PROFICIENCIES**

- Front-end web languages (HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript)
- Python (including Flask and Django)
- Selenium
- Database (SQL, MongoDB, Postgres)
- Shopify
- webscraper.io
- AWS
- Software best practices
- Web development projects
- · Quick learner
- Can-do attitude
- No visa required